-t-t-t-t
-t
It's enough crying.
And enough sitting around.
It's time to make a decision.
I've got to go.
They're all fighting for me.
Please.
Breathe.
You need to come back now!
Before it's too late!
For your friends.
I must have been dreaming.
For a moment there?
I thought we actually had a chance.
Uh, so what did that shark
guy just do? I don't know.
It looked like he was just
throwing water around.
But then they both started to bleed.
I don't even have to touch you.
You humans are so fragile
that I can kill you
just by playing around
with a little water.
That's the difference between you and me.
Shut up!
He's not kidding.
That's why the shark
is king of the fishmen.
He's on a whole different level.
You should just die.
Your lives are not worth that much.
There's no one who will
miss you when you're gone.
Arlong!
It's Nami.
You're here.
Hey, Nami.
I was just teaching one final lesson
to these pathetic little pirates.
What are you doing here?
I'm here to kill you.
Wealth, fame, power.
Gold Roger, the king of the pirates,
attained this and everything
else the world had to offer.
and his dying words drove
countless souls to the seas.
You want my treasure?
You can have it.
I left everything I gathered
together in one place.
Now you just have to find it.
These words lured men to
the Grand Line in pursuit
of dreams greater than
they'd ever dared to imagine.
This is the time known
as the Great Pirate Era.
Come aboard and bring along
all your hopes and dreams.
Together we will find everything
that we're looking for.
One piece.
Compass left behind,
he'll only slow us down.
Your heart will be your guide,
raise the sails and take the helm.
That legendary place that
the end of the map reveals.
It's only legendary until
someone proves it real.
Through it all, through
all the trouble of times.
Through the heartache
and through the pain.
Know that I will be there to stand by you.
Just like I know you'll stand by me.
So come aboard and bring along
all your hopes and dreams.
Together we will find everything
that we're looking for.
There's always room for you.
If you wanna be my friend.
We are, we are on a cruise.
We are
Me?
You want to kill me?
hasn't you learned your lesson
yet how many times have you tried
to kill me in these last eight
years um you've tried Assassination
um
you must be aware that you
mere humans can't kill me
Now listen, I won't put you in the
ground, Nami But you can't leave
You will remain here, with
us, as our surveyor, forever
But as you know,
I'm quite good-natured If possible,
I'd like you to be our
surveyor of your own free will
I'm giving you a choice.
I will not take pause in having my fishmen
kill every living creature on this island.
Except for you.
But that's only if you
refuse to come back to the
Arlong Pirates and draw sea
sharks as one of our own.
And if you decide to come back with us,
I'll be kind and spare
the villagers their lives.
But I can't let these ingrates live.
They must be made an example of.
So there's only one question!
Will you come with me and save
the people of Cocoyashi village?
Or be foolish and refuse my
request by fighting alongside them?
It's your choice!
With them you will be hopeless.
With them you will die.
Nami.
Will you come and stand by my side?
Or not?
The decision is yours.
This isn't fair.
If I remain friends with Luffy and
the others, everyone will be killed.
But if I go with Arlong, everyone
from the village will be saved.
Their lives depend on my choice.
Not fair!
No matter what she chooses,
he'll never set her free!
But...
Luffy...
Help me...
That's for Nami!
I have to believe in him!
All right, everyone, we'll
fight to the death, got it?
Well then, it looks like
they've made up their minds.
Please, Liv! Please, Liv!
Alright, now just remove his leg weight.
I see.
That's what you meant.
No way!
Luffy's alive!
Hey! Hang in there!
You can't give up now!
Thirty seconds.
That's all I've got.
Zoro!
That'll be enough!
There isn't a fountain over there.
Could it be that rubber man?
Just stay back.
You're not getting anywhere near him.
Ah, Zoro.
I thought I told you to
never say that again.
Now prepare to die!
If I kick and break that
leg weight, he can fight.
Luffy, you're the only
one who can fight now.
In the sea,
one with Devil Fruit powers is supposed
to lose even the energy to struggle.
Not to mention his powers.
He will die.
And if he's still alive,
well, that wouldn't be fair.
You okay?
hey Lisa you're fine sure I'm fine
you scared us where'd your pinwheel
go it was cool we've got bigger things
to worry about right now wouldn't
be fair this game hasn't been fair
from the moment we started playing
it well anyways if there's a hindrance
I should be aware of it correct
I've got your back, Zoro!
Big bro Usopp, he's all right!
How brave!
And he got here just in time.
Go on, give it to him!
That's where you are?
He's all right!
Hey, hey, Nami!
I beat one of their
leaders, can you believe it?
I wiped the smug off his stupid face!
Think, is there any way
you can free yourself?
Nope, can't do it.
The energy is way too low.
C'mon! C'mon! C'mon! C'mon!
All right, cook!
Now, if they can just
set Big Bro Luffy free,
the fishmen will be running
for their lives! Go, Zoro!
Take down Arlong once and for all!
Okay, we have to somehow prevent
Arlong from getting into the sea.
I'll just keep him from going anywhere.
I won't let you have your way.
Hey, Harlong, I've got a present for you!
What's he doing?
He's so brave!
You seem to keep standing in my way.
I take it you wish to die first, then.
I can take care of that.
Zoro, now!
What do you think you're doing, Usopp?
Now's my chance.
All I want is a piece of that...
You fool.
It's a proud nose
because it's unbreakable.
If you were in full strength,
you may have been able to
give it a little scratch.
Look over there that damn octopus is up
What?!
He's the one I was aiming for!
But weren't you yelling Arlong, huh?
Oh, great.
We're not done, Zoro!
You may have put me down,
but it wasn't for good!
Cause I'm still alive and now
I'm gonna finish off your friend!
No need to be concerned seeing as
how you will all be dead anyway
You've done enough, Nojiko.
Leave the rest to me!
Watch out!
I'll break the rock with a kick!
What?
Octopus-Fla-Renzy!
No!
Thoreau!
So, that's it, huh?
Way too easy.
What's with all these bandages?
Did you have a good fall?
What's this scar?
I can't believe he's breathing how can
he still be alive with a body like this
Is he dying already?
Am I fighting a wounded man?
Either way, he's about to die.
He's going to die right here and now.
If a person stays put,
their wounds won't open up.
Is that right?
Do you find your situation amusing?
I'm not talking about me.
I'm talking about the Octoman.
What?
I thought we told you.
We'll win this game.
That was too close.
You're the one that made this
complicated in the first place.
He did it!
It's time to take care of that shark.
Hurry up, you idiot!
Did they free you? Yes!
It's him!
A hero back!
Luffy!
That rubber bastard!
You're a bit late.
Hey, hold on.
What are you...
Let's switch!
You idiot!
Come go!
Oh, no! Oh, that way!
Oh, no!
Take care!
Help me!
Yes!
Is that all you got?
It's not working!
Nope, just a warm one.
Ugh.
That idiot.
I'm gonna kill him.
What a bunch of fools.
You think you can actually beat me?
You were better off
drowning on the ocean floor.
No, I don't think so.
I like it up here. Yep.
Do you not understand my anger?
I saw my brothers crushed like worms.
You'll realize soon enough that you
should have quit fighting a long time ago.
Do you think Luffy's gonna be okay?
I mean, Arlong doesn't seem to be
affected by his attacks at all.
And more importantly, just how
far away do you think Zoro flew?
Luffy!
I got your back, pal!
No need to worry.
If he loses, then we'll all die.
Yeah, we will.
If that happens, it's the
end of the East Blue, too.
Do you know what the biggest difference
between you and me is the nose?
The jaw.
Um what's he doing uh
i don't know webbing.
Species!
Oh, man!
I bet that had to be painful!
His teeth must be shattered!
You see this is the
inherent power of this man.
I feel sorry for you, pathetic humans,
having been created with such limited power.
We've been on a different level than
you since the beginning of time.
Being such inferior creatures, it makes
perfect sense for you to bow before me.
He's right.
There's no way a human could
do something like that.
If those jaws got a hold of you,
they would do a lot more than
just leave some bite marks.
He'll snap through your
bones like a butcher.
Yeah, so what?
Quit your bragging.
You're not that awesome.
Besides, smashing stones with
your teeth isn't that smart.
Way to go, you're the best, big bro.
Tell it like it is. Yeah.
What idiot bites a rock anyway?
Fools.
That's not the point.
Every member of the human
race is ignorant and weak.
What good are you if you can't even
pull yourself out of the water?
As a matter of fact, I'm worthless
without my friends to help me out.
Huh? No way!
Luffy's a swordsman?
Huh?
Is this a joke?
Whatever it is, it isn't swordplay.
You're just flailing about
like a child playing pirates.
I hope you realize this isn't a game.
That's enough! Now die!
Shut your face!
What?!
He just shattered our mom's tea!
You're right!
I don't have a clue how to
use a sword, you bastard!
Wait, what exactly is
he trying to say here?
I'm a terrible sailor.
I definitely can't cook.
And I can't even lie! Hey!
And without my friends to help me, I
would have been dead a long time ago!
So you fully admit how pathetic you are.
You may be a fool, but
you certainly are honest.
How must your crew feel tolerating
this idiocy day in and day out?
I bet they're sick of it.
But that makes me wonder why they tried so
desperately to save their half-wit leader.
Someone like you doesn't
deserve a ship or a crew.
What good is a helpless
rubber-brained captain to them?
What can you possibly do?
I can kick your ass!
Well, get to it, you numbskull.
If he dies, I'm going to kill him.
I've got your back, Luffy.
All right, Kong!
Let it be!
Yeah, go for it!
Cheer all you want, but
it won't change a thing.
He's got no teeth.
I'm a shark.
New teeth will grow one after another.
And with each set, they
become stronger and stronger.
Endlessly.
As many as it takes.
This is but one of the many
gifts we fistmen possess.
That's so cool!
If you haven't yet realized that these
men are superior, you will very soon.
Tooth, attack!
Let's roll of me!
Our long leaps.
It hurts.
What?
My brother!
You're dead, you stretchy freak!
How dare you use my injured
brother as a shield?
What are you talking about?
You're the one who attacked me!
Don't you remember that was pretty scary?
Don't move a muscle!
Rubber man!
Hey!
Now that's an interesting idea!
He's got an idea!
It's in his brain!
Did he come up with?
With some secret scheme?
All right!
You.
You fool.
There's no point in crushing my teeth.
You really don't get it!
Big Bro, Luffy, that
can't be very sanitary.
So what?
Now I have short teeth!
How long do you intend
to keep fooling around?
Don't beat me!
So stop playing games!
It's not like I'm having fun!
Unattack!
Oh, no!
Gotcha!
And now we're even!
So you used my tea.
But your puny jaws aren't strong enough.
Now listen, sharp as my teeth are,
they're only useful when they
come with powerful jaws like mine.
Then they're DEADLY!
Ah!
Big Bro's gonna get his arm bitten off!
All that's in my heart confuses
me, I cannot understand.
As I face what I must do, I'll
say goodbye and squeeze your hand!
I'll set sail alone, but always
know I'm dying, I'll keep you near.
As I drift away, I pray you
watch me as I disappear.
As I watched the sunrise,
I began to wonder?
What could be the reason
it's so hot inside?
No answer has come, but I can't
get away from what's true.
It's because of you!
Show me how to catch those feelings,
get them to come back to me?
I'll do what I must because
they're everything I want of me.
Wrap these arms around my dreams
and pull them back from yesterday.
If I'm holding hands with you,
I'm sure that we can make a way!